(Penny:)Sheldon, what took you so long?
(Sheldon:)Wolowitz might
hand out cigars.
(Sheldon:)I had to find my bubble gum
(Sheldon:)cigar so I could join in
without looking foolish.
(Leonard:)Damn, I need my inhaler.
(Amy:)Just don't smoke.
(Leonard:)No, I went down
the stairs too fast.
(Sheldon:)Hey.
(Raj:)Don't come to the hospital.
We're headed home.
(Penny:)Oh, that was fast.
Did she sneeze the baby out?
(Bernadette:)We showed up too early.
We'll keep you posted.
(Penny:)Okay, well, we'll
(Penny:)talk to you guys later. Bye.
(Penny:)She said not to come.
It's gonna be a while.
(Amy:)Well, first deliveries
can be slow.
I am starting to rethink the
Flash onesie I bought this kid.
(Leonard:)I found it,
but it's empty.
(Penny:)Well, it doesn't matter. We're
not going to the hospital now.
(Leonard:)Are you sure?
I'd really like to.
(Amy:)Well, should we,
uh, head back up?
Come on, guys.
(Penny:)We're all awake. Why don't we go
to a diner or something?
(Amy:)Oh, uh, I don't know.
(Amy:)Sheldon, you don't want
to do that, do you?